你要打網球嗎
You taking up tennis?
不  這是個蒼蠅拍
No, it's a fly swatter.
我想看看這東西怎么用
I want to see it work.
那也要有只蒼蠅啊
Well, we need a fly.
我已經等了一早上了
I've been waiting whole morning.
你剛剛是打死了一只嗎
Did you honestly just kill one?
怎么了  伙計們
Hey, what's going on, guys?
走路要有尊嚴  跟個剛學步的孩子似的
Walk with dignity, you giant toddler.
得了吧  施密特  你得把這些搬走
Come on, Schmidt, you got to get this stuff out of here, man.
我也想  可是我付不起租倉庫的錢
Yeah, well, I can't afford storage.
我的錢都用光了
All my money's tied up
都給杰茜的姐姐付店面租金了
in the storefront I leased for Jess' sister.
那你為什么不把這堆垃圾
So why don't you put your junk
放在店面里呢  施密特
in the storefront, Schmidt?
你真的想讓我把伊恩·施拉格的地毯
You really want me to put an Ian Schrager rug
精品酒店創始人及同名酒店
與萬豪酒店聯合推出Edition酒店品牌
放在沒有恒溫空調的房間里嗎
in a room without climate control?
什么
What?
是《星球大戰》里的那個人啊
Oh, he was the guy in Star Wars.
那可是個公關人才
Medium talent.
伙計們  早上好
Hey, guys. Morning.
-早上好  杰茜  -早上好
- Hey, Jess. - Hey.
快點  教練  我們得趕緊走了
Come on, Coach! Let's hustle!
我幫教練在學校找了份工作
I got Coach a job at the school,
今天是他第一天上班
and it's his first day.
我不喜歡小孩  我也不喜歡教課
I don't like kids, I don't like teaching,
我只喜歡領薪水
I just like paychecks.
我覺得你會愛上這工作的
Well, I think you're gonna love it.
我不這么覺得
I don't think I'm gonna love it.
跑起來  不要停
Run! Do not stop running
要不然我生吞了你們
or I will eat your faces and bodies!
接著跑  不然我殺了你全家
Keep running or I will murder your family!
我愛這份工作
I love this job.
你惹火我了  就說你呢
You're pissing me off! This one.
就你  我盯著你呢
This one. I got my eye on you.
■
本字幕由人人影視字幕組翻譯
禁止用作任何商業盈利行為
杰茜駕到  第三季第十九集
謝謝你們幫我搬東西
Thanks for helping me move my stuff, you guys.
*好多討厭的盒子*
*Lots of hairy boxes*
天吶  我破產了
God, I've fallen.
快比你還慘了  尼克
Almost below you now, Nick.
難兄難弟們  一起生活在社會的底層
Fellow passengers, stuck in the caboose of life.
你覺得我生活在社會底層嗎
You think I'm in the caboose of life?
翻譯：瑤莞莞 兮之 樂小樂樂樂
你喜歡這樣的生活  我卻不然
You love it in the caboose, not me.
雖然這很傷人  事實上也相當刺耳
It hurts. It's actually quite jarring.
翻譯：沐頭 小明漫畫家 MythCreator
*熱愛底層的生活*
*Loves it in the caboose*
我可不喜歡生活在社會底層
I don't love it in the caboose.
*其實他很喜歡*
*Yes, he does.*
時間軸：Chance-Coco 糖不甩   后期：MythCreator
你們好  這里營業嗎
Uh, hi. Are you guys open?
這里其實不是商店
Oh, this actually... It's not a store.
那太可惜了
Oh. That's too bad.
校對：持久君 麥田守望者  總監:  丟丟曳  特別鳴謝：衛老哥
我真的很喜歡那盞燈
I really like that lamp.
你喜歡那盞燈嗎
You like... you like the lamp?
不好意思  你知道嗎
I'm sorry. You know what, it just...
這里只是  看起來不像個商店而已
it's just that... it doesn't... it doesn't feel like a store yet
這才是我想表達的意思
is what I meant to say.
鋼琴彈得很動人
Piano player is a nice touch.
謝謝你  他很棒  不是嗎
Aw, thank you very much. He's lovely, isn't he?
請四處看看  隨便看
Pl- please look around. Feel free.
那盞燈不打折
The lamp is 100% full price.
這里幾乎所有東西都不打折的
Uh, pretty much everything's 100% full price.
你這樣做是違法的
What you're doing is illegal.
你不能說這是家商店
You can't say this is a store.
我才不要聽你的
I'm not taking advice from you,
"千層面"這詞  你都能念成"千成面"
you pronounce the "G" in "Lasagna."
千...成面
Lasag-na.
我的天  我的手臂好像折了
Oh, my God. I think my arm's broken.
我要把你告到傾家蕩產
I'm gonna sue the crap out of you.
溫斯頓  安靜點
Winston! Quiet.
我第四節課  我跟賈馬爾·錢伯斯聊了會兒
So, I have Jamal Chambers in my fourth period,
他不停地跟我說  新來的排球教練
and he cannot stop talking about how fun
有多幽默又熱情
and enthusiastic his new volleyball coach was.
你說對了  我愛這份工作
You were right. I love this job.
我就知道你會喜歡的
I knew it. I knew you'd love it.
-你好啊  -我正找你呢
- Hey. - I was looking for you.
你不在我車里  我的網斷了
You weren't in my car. Internet's down.
好吧  我重啟了路由器
Okay, um, well, I rebooted the router.
你搞錯IP地址了  所以
You're actually on the wrong IP address, so...
搞定
There you go.
你知道我能看見你的搜索歷史吧
You know I can see everything that you search for, right?
我是一名生物老師  這都是為了做研究
I'm a biology teacher. It's all research.
你現在還負責修電腦什么的嗎
Fixing computers and stuff now?
我只是多攬些擔子而已
I'm just taking on a little extra responsibility around here,
把該做的事都做好
just getting stuff done that needs doing.
孩子們  在墻上亂涂鴉不好
Graffiti's wrong, kids.
以后別這樣了
Don't do it.
我也喜歡玉米棒
I love corn on the cob, too,
但我不會把它畫得滿墻都是
but I'm not gonna paint it all over the walls.
我只是希望  幾年后
I'm just hoping, you know, in a few years
我能積累足夠的經驗
I'll have enough experience
使得福斯特博士  能考慮讓我做副校長
that Dr. Foster will consider me for vice principal.
你為什么不直接跟他談談呢
Why don't you just ask him for it?
你不能主動要求升職的
You can't just ask for a promotion. You know.
你得通過幾年的辛勤工作  來獲得晉升
You have to earn the promotion with years of good work.
有什么好笑的
What's funny?
你怎么就這么不開竅呢  杰茜
Uh, how's that working out for you, Jess?
你看見這排球了嗎
Do you see this volleyball?
不是你想讓它過網  它就能過的
It won't get over the net just because you want it to.
你寄望于有人會發現你想要當副校長
and you hope someone will notice that you want it to.
我再問你一次
I'm gonna ask you one more time:
你  想要  什么
what... do you... want?
我想要當副校長
Um, I want to be vice principal.
好  那就把這個球打回來  杰茜
All right. Then spike that ball, Jess.
那可不  好吧
Oh, that's not... Okay...
打回來  打回來
You got to spike! You got to spike!
非得  好吧
Is that really... Yeah. Okay.
不  等等  我不是很擅長
No, wait. I'm not very good...
打回來
Spike it!
我一直不擅長球類運動
I've just never really been good with athlete balls.
打回來打回來
Spike it! Spike it!
-你想要什么  -我想當副校長
- What do you want?! - I want to be vice principal.
把球打回來然后告訴我你想要什么
Spike the ball and tell me what you want!
我想當副校長
I want to be the vice principal!
我不會笑你的
I will not laugh.
氣死我了
An outrage!
我到處找  都找不到請得起的律師
Been all over and I can't afford anybody.
難以置信
Unbelievable.
能夠找到高級法律顧問
Access to premium legal counsel
應該是每個猶太人與生俱來的權利
should be every Jew's birthright.
陪審團會看到
And the jury will see
對希伯來人而言毫無公平
that there is no justice for the Hebrew man.
至少不在這美利堅合眾國
Not in these so-called United States.
你們到底在干嗎
What is that that you're doing?
我太喜歡這些法律劇了
I can't get enough of this legal drama.
你看吧  最喜歡的作者是格里森姆
Check this out. Favorite author, Grisham.
最喜歡的電視劇  《法外柔情》
Favorite TV show, Judging Amy.
最喜歡的顏色  法庭的棕色
Favorite color, courtroom brown.
法庭棕  我真希望那是我的昵稱
Courtroom Brown. Damn, I wish that was my nickname.
你是突然想到的嗎  這名字太棒了
Did you just think of that 'cause it was perfect, man?
法庭棕
Courtroom Brown.
伙計  你生來就該叫法庭棕的
Dude, you're a born Courtroom Brown.
我就叫法庭棕  你說法庭棕我就會有反應
That's me. When you say "Courtroom Brown", I respond.
溫斯頓
Hey, Winston.
-法庭棕  -有事嗎
- Hey, Courtroom Brown. - Yes?
真棒  法庭棕  太棒了
Kill 'em, Courtroom Brown! That's awesome!
這種情況下我該怎么辦
What am I supposed to do in this situation,
像某些瘋子一樣  自己代表自己嗎
represent myself like some nut job?
尼克可以當你的律師啊
Nick could be your lawyer.
這個尼克嗎  半途輟學小姐
This Nick? Vivica A. Dropout?
首先  我并不想參與其中
First of all, I don't want to be involved,
但謝謝你  法庭棕
but thank you, Courtroom Brown.
其次  我通過律師測試了  也就是說
And second of all, I passed the bar, which means
我可以在加州做律師
I can practice in the state of California.
尼克  那你肯定是世界上最差的律師
Nick, you would be the worst in the whole entire world.
無意冒犯  我愛你  哥們
No offense. I love you, dawg.
當你的律師輕而易舉
I could be your lawyer easy.
我不會忘記怎么當律師  這就像騎自行車
You don't forget how to be a lawyer. It's like riding a bike.
他們肯定改裝過
They've changed these!
好吧  我忘了該如何騎自行車
Fine. I forgot how to ride a bike.
但我不會忘記如何做律師
But I'm not gonna forget how to be a lawyer.
我看我也別無選擇  尼克你可以做我的律師
I guess I have no choice. You can be my lawyer, Nick.
我不會做你的律師的
I won't do it.
我認為自己太棒了  不值得這樣做
I value myself too great for that.
如果你想讓我做你的律師
If you want me to be your lawyer,
如果你想贏這個案子  你必須
if you want to win this case, you must start
先說個"請"字
with the word "please".
而且我還要象征性地收五塊錢的費用
And I'll need a symbolic five-dollar retainer.
四塊
Four dollars.
成吧  成交
Skin it. Let's do it.
福斯特博士  我年輕且活力充沛
Dr. Foster, I am young, I'm energetic
我覺得你該好好的占占我的便宜了
and I think it's about time you take advantage of me!
這  有點尷尬啊
Well, this is... a little awkward.
我  我只對亞洲女人感興趣
I'm, uh... I'm exclusively into Asian women.
我喜歡克麗斯蒂·山口[花滑隊員]這型
It's really a Kristi Yamaguchi thing.
那是在利勒哈默爾冬奧會之后
After Lillehammer...
我是指工作上
I really meant professionally--
我想讓你在工作上多重用我
I want you to take advantage of me like that.
抱歉
Oh. I'm sorry.
-是工作上的事情  -是的  抱歉
- It's a professional thing. - Okay. Sorry.
我想當副校長
I want to be vice principal.
弗蘭克退休后你需要人手  這是我應得的
Frank retired, you need someone. I deserve it.
我為這所學校竭盡全力
I bust my ass for this school.
你成功了  這位置是你的了
You've got it. The job is yours.
-真的嗎  -天吶  肯定啊
- It is? - Oh, my God, are you kidding?
我還以為我得逼著某人來當副校長呢
I thought I was gonna have to force somebody into it.
這就容易多了
This is so much easier.
-真的嗎  -去做吧
- Really? - Go ahead.
你就是副校長了
Be vice principal.
我簡直不敢相信
I can't believe this.
事實上  我認為
In fact, I think
你應該現在就開始著手了
you should start right now.
你不會后悔的  長官
You will not be sorry, sir.
成功了嗎
Did you?
我得到這份工作了
I got the job!
-我打到那個球了  -該慶祝慶祝了
- I spiked the ball. - Time to celebrate.
不不  我才不做那個呢
No! No! I'm not doing that!
-不  -我們得慶祝慶祝啊
- No! - We got to celebrate! Celebrate!
不
No!
讓我把這潑到你臉上衣服上頭發上
Let me pour it on your face and your clothes and your hair!
看起來很規范的樣子
Yeah. Looks standard.
你肯定是被起訴了
You're definitely being sued.
你明天要去錄口供
Uh, your deposition is tomorrow.
我們現在怎么辦  我們要了解一下原告嗎
What-what do we do now? Do we prep for the plaintiff?
我不喜歡做準備工作  那會讓我緊張
I don't like prepping. It makes me feel nervous.
我會覺得我被困住了
I feel boxed in.
-我那個...很麻利的  -當然了
- And I'm very quick on my, uh... - Sure.
你是忘了"手腳"這個詞怎么說嗎
Did you just forget the word "feet"?
手腳  沒錯
Feet. Yeah.
尼克  你該準備一下
Nick, you should really prep.
有道理  溫斯頓  你就當原告
Fair enough. Winston, you're my plaintiff.
-行啊  -好的
- Done deal. - Okay.
我叫提姆·貝克
Hi, my name is Tim Baker.
我住在杜甘法院露臺522號
I live at 522 Dugan Court Terrace.
好  貝克先生  你做廚師多久了
Okay, Mr. Baker, how long have you been a chef?
這我不必回答
I don't have to answer that.
事實上你必須回答  溫斯頓
You actually do though, Winston.
是吧
Doesn't he?
你問我  干嗎來問我
You ask... Why you asking me, man?
我沒問你  我知道
No, I'm not. I'm... Yeah. No, I know.
你是律師啊
You're the lawyer.
你得回答這個  你做廚師多久了
You have to answer. How long you been a chef?
那個我在背景介紹里答過了
I already answered that during background.
什么  你們做背景介紹沒叫我
What in the hell? You did background without me?
為什么不叫我
Why wasn't I invited for background?
你必須得回答  做廚師多久了
You have to answer it! How long you been a chef?!
你被炒了
You're fired!
再給我一次機會吧
Give me another chance.
不
No!
這樣行不行  和我一起走吧  坐飛機
Okay, here's something. Get on a plane with me.
考慮一下吧  這杯從我卡上刷
While you think about it, put this on my card.
黑色那張
It's the black one.
真有這種事發生
Wow. That just happened.
你覺得我們要不要刷他的卡
You think maybe we should take his card
給他買件像樣點的衣服
and buy him a new shirt?
我怕他會在我們面前換衣服
I'm scared he'd want to change it in front of us.
我叫希希
I'm Cece.
嗨  希希  我是巴斯特
Hi, Cece. I'm Buster.
這不會是你真名吧
I really hope that's a nickname.
是真名
No, it's not a nickname.
你真叫這個嗎
It's your real name?
原來我就因為這個被欺負得很慘
I was bullied pretty bad.
你好啊  巴斯特
Hi, Buster.
慢著  我看小年輕可準了
All right, hold on. I've got quite an eye for young boys.
老天吶
Oh, God.
沒錯  你沒聽錯  我就是那意思
That's right, I said it, it's not a typo.
身份證給我看看
Let's see some I.D.
老天  你真帥
God, you're handsome.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
懷俄明州的
Wyoming!
看看  懷俄明州誒
Look at that. Wyoming.
原來你是懷州三人組組員之一啊
So you're one of the three people from Wyoming.
牛仔國度  藍天之城  自由鐘之鄉
Yeah. Cowboy state, big sky country, home of the Liberty Bell.
凈瞎扯
Bull... snatch.
口音真難聽
That's an awful accent.
你真實的口音是怎樣的
What is your real accent?
你是澳洲來的  還是星星上來的
Are you Australian or from Heaven?
你到底多大了
How old are you, for real?
-別這樣  -別和我耍花樣
- Leave him alone. - Don't bull-snatch a bull-snatcher.
別惹他了  你有21歲了  對吧
Leave him alone. You're over 21, right?
沒有
I'm not.
我20歲
Um... I'm 20.
快滾出去  你這帥死了的混蛋
Get out of here, you delicious bastard.
身份證可以還我了嗎
Can I get my I.D. Back?
當然不行  你不能喝酒
No, of course not, you can't.
那樣是違法的  你真是太完美了
It'd be against the law, you... wonderful creature.
很高興認識你  希希
Nice to meet you, Cece.
老天吶  你真是帥
Good God, you look nice.
未到法定年齡就喝酒的人最讓我惱火了
Nothing irks me like underage drinking.
又蠢  又危險  還不負責任
It's stupid, it's dangerous, it's irresponsible.
老天  我太想和那孩子上床了
God, I want to have sex with that kid so bad,
我都要瘋了
it's freaking me out!
真是心癢癢
Oh... I'm real tingly.
我們得談談預算的事
We have talk about the budget.
預算有問題嗎  可是期限是到周一啊
There's a problem with the budget? But it's due Monday.
-沒錯  -難道是我們錢太多了
- Yeah. - Do we have too much money?
-不是  -我們得炒掉幾個人
- No. - We need to fire people.
-什么  -我說的我們  是指你
- What? - And when I say "We," I mean you.
從新進職員開始
Start with the most recent hires.
新進的有  歷史系的珍妮特
Well, we have, um... Janet from the history department.
沒用的廢物
Human garbage.
好吧
Okay.
厄尼
Ernie, uh...
沒錯
Ah, yeah.
不對  是教練
No. That's Coach.
不行  不行  不行
No. No. No.
這不行  他做的很不錯
No, he's very good at his job.
最后進來的最先走人  事情就是這樣
Last one in, first one out-- you know how this works.
-這不對  -這是你的工作  戴小姐
- That's just wrong. - This is the job, Ms. Day.
他是我的朋友  我不能這么做
He's my friend. I can't. No.
我不會炒他的  絕對不會
I'm not doing it. I'm not firing Coach.
這是你的工作  戴小姐
This is the job, Ms. Day.
你到底做還是不做
Do you want it or not?
你說什么
I'm what?
我們必須縮減預算
We had to do budget cuts,
所以必須得開除兩個人
and we have to let two people go,
你是我朋友  可我無能為力
and you're my friend, and I couldn't stop it.
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
我們都投進了
We all pitched in.
謝謝了  伙計們
Thanks, guys,
可我不再是你們的教練了
I'm not coach anymore.
我是名不副實的"教練"
I'm just Coach.
-什么  -什么
- What? - What?
早上好  溫斯頓
Morning, Winston.
你不準備和我說話了嗎
Are you not talking to me?
聽著  炒教練魷魚是我的職責
Look, I had to fire Coach for my job.
我也不想這樣
I didn't want to.
別這么斜眼看我
Don't squint at me.
別這樣
Don't do that.
那是工作需要  我別無選擇
I did it for my job. It wasn't my choice.
-尼克  你好啊  -溫尼  你好
- Hey, Nick, what's up, man? - What's up, Winnie?
-尼克  -你好
- Hey, Nick. - Hey.
-我能跟你聊下嗎  -我可以先說嗎
- Can we talk for a second? - Can I talk to you?
施密特把我炒魷魚了
Schmidt fired me,
我再沒機會用這款新買的包包了
and now I'll never get to use this briefcase I just bought,
花了我十九塊呢
and it was $19!
我覺得我的事情稍微更
I think my thing is a little bit more...
你覺得我是提著包性感還是垂著更性感
Do you think I'm sexier when I hold it or when it's down?
因為我覺得這樣提著挺性感的
'Cause I think it's kind of sexier when I hold it, like this.
-算不上  -我看起來像有權勢的人嗎
- Not really. - Do I look like a man of power?
想象下這個畫面  一個雨天
Imagine this-- it's, like, a rainy day,
我在紐約的街頭
I'm on the streets of New York.
等等  出租車
Hey! Stop that cab!
我是個商人  要趕一場重要的會議
I'm a businessman. I'm late to an important meeting.
我真心覺得我會很適合的
I honestly feel like I would've been so good at this.
你都不想當律師
You don't want to be a lawyer--
為什么還要在意施密特是否炒你魷魚
why do you care whether Schmidt fired you or not?
那些年我在法學院遇到的預科混蛋們
I spent all those years at law school with those preppy dicks...
我從沒機會向他們證明我的實力  杰茜
and I never got to prove them wrong, Jess.
行啊  去追求你想要的東西吧
Okay, go after what you want.
只要保證你所想要的
Just make sure that what you want...
不會讓你變成病態系統中的小齒輪
doesn't make you a cog on the wheel of a larger, flawed system.
夠了  不要說了
Stop it. Shut your mouth.
因為你的話語太美了
'Cause what you're saying is beautiful.
我這就去穿上我的權勢西裝
I'm gonna go put on my power suit.
舉起手來為我歡呼吧
High and loud, girl.
很好的溝通  尼克
Good talk, Nick.
有了這個  我感覺好性感喲
With this thing, I feel so sexy,
我都好羞羞啊
it's disgusting.
我覺得你沒懂...
I think you misunderstood...
-你的代表人遲到了嗎  -不是的
- Your representation running late? - Uh, no.
事實上  我今天要自己來
Actually, I'll be representing myself today.
抱歉  我們遲到了  這地方太混亂了
Sorry we're late. This building is a total mess.
我是尼克·米勒  庫珀  貝肖普和弗格森事務所的
Nick Miller of, uh, Cooper, Bishop and Furguson.
我的老板和高級合伙人  溫斯頓·弗格森
As you know, my boss and senior partner, Mr. Winston Furguson.
先生們  很高興認識你們
Gentlemen, pleased to be with you.
別  千萬別站起來  不用起來
Please, please don't get up, don't get up.
我堅持
I-I insist.
秘書女士
Madam Secretary.
-你來干什么  -我來為你辯護
- What are you doing here? - I'm representing you.
-一切都好嗎  -我有點措手不及
- Everything all right? - I'm a bit caught off guard.
我沒想到他們兩個真律師會出現
I wasn't expecting these two very real lawyers to show up today.
我們希望你知道
Well, we wanted to let you know that
整個公司都支持你
the entire firm is standing behind you.
而且  無論我是在這里還是在辦公司
Besides, whether I sit in my office or in here...
我都是有錢收的  對吧  先生們
it's all billable-- am I right, gentlemen?
是直切主題呢  還是脫褲子呢
Shall we get into this, or just take our pants off?
快問他問題
Ask him a question.
-讓我  讓我自己來  -你快點
- Let me... let me do my thing. - Do your thing.
貝克先生
Mr. Baker.
是的
Yes?
你家住址多少
What's your home address?
杜根排屋五二二號
522 Dugan Court Terrace.
好的
Okay.
沒有...沒有問題了
Uh, no... no further questions.
什么
What?
繼續問啊
Keep going.
-繼續問啊  -你到底
- Just keep going. - What are you...
別打我啊  你打我做什么
Don't hit me. What are you hitting me for?
-你們還好嗎  -當然  還在計時呢
- Is everything all right? - Sure it is. The meter's running.
就算你不在柯立芝工作了
Even though you don't work at Coolidge anymore,
你還是孩子們的小教練
you'll still be Coach Coach to those kids.
小教練
It's Coach Coach.
對啊  小教練
Yeah, Coach Coach.
-小教練  -小教
- Coach Coach. - Coach Coa...
-小教練  -我錯了
- Coach Coach. - I'm sorry.
杰茜  沒事的
It's all good, Jess.
你只是在盡責而已
You did what you had to do.
我為你驕傲  好嗎
I'm proud of you for that, okay?
-好  -我希望我是你裁員大軍的第一個
- Yeah. - I hope I'm the first of many you fire.
你這么想  真的對我很重要
That really means a lot to me.
雖然我真的很想念孩子們
I am gonna miss those kids, though.
-對  -這就是我會想的
- Yeah. - That's what I'm gonna miss.
那些  那些小混蛋們
Those little... those little bastards.
小羅尼
Little Ronnie.
羅尼又慢又笨
Ronnie's so clumsy and slow.
-是啊  -還有托馬斯
- Yeah. - Thomas.
他很強壯  但是他就是典型的中產階級小孩
I mean, he's strong, but that boy is a classic middle child.
整天就想著愛情
He's just looking for love, up, back and sideways.
還有莫里斯
And Maurice.
他一吃棒冰就吃一臉啊
He always makes a mess whenever he eats a Popsicle.
就想跟他說
It's, like, dude,
別再那樣吃棒冰啦
stop sucking your Popsicle like that, man.
你這樣永遠沒有女朋友的
You're never gonna get a girlfriend like that.
還有漢特
And then there's Hunter.
肥嘟嘟的  還有斜視眼
Fat... cross-eyed...
粗魯的漢特
clod-hopping Hunter.
漢特是最可愛的小笨蛋
Hunter is the sweetest little idiot there ever was.
他好貼心的
He's so sweet!
我不管了
Screw this!
因為你告訴過我
Because... you told me...
去追求自己想要的  可這不是我想要的
to go after what I wanted, and this is not what I wanted.
來吧  我們來想辦法讓你重返賽場
Let's go! We're gonna get you to that game!
還是算了  他們在和帕薩迪納打比賽
It's okay. They're playing Pasadena.
他們沒有希望的
They don't stand a chance.
帕薩迪納的人都是耍賤招滑頭
Pasadena has a bunch of bitch-ass tricks.
沒有教養
Weren't raised right.
你真心想要的是什么
Hey, what do you want?
我不知道  我想去
I don't know. I want to be there.
去扣殺吧
So, spike that ball!
那可不是球  那是啤酒
That was not a ball. That was beer.
我知道  我很內疚
I know. I feel really bad about it.
-你猜怎么的  別內疚  -向前沖吧
- You know what? Don't feel bad! - Let's go!
-向前沖吧  -你讓我熱血沸騰
- Let's go! - You got me all fired up!
估計車子得你開了
I think you're gonna have to drive.
米勒先生說  "你是否曾經在商店里
Mr. Miller: "Were you or were you not
穿大于自己實際號碼的鞋子"
wearing oversized shoes in the store?"
貝克先生說  "沒有過  我告訴過你"
Mr. Becker: "I was not. I told you that."
米勒先生說  "你確定嗎"  施密特先生說  "閉嘴  尼克"
Mr. Miller: "But are you sure?" Mr. Schmidt: "Shut up, Nick."
米勒先生說  "交給我處理吧  住手"
Mr. Miller: "Let me do this. Ow. Stop it."
施密特先生說  "住什么手  是你自己打的"
Mr. Schmidt: "Stop what? You're hitting yourself."
米勒先生說  "你是小孩嗎"
Mr. Miller: "You're a child."
施密特先生說  "小孩當律師都能比你當得好"
Mr. Schmidt: "A child would be a better lawyer."
弗格森先生說  "孩子承載著未來"
Mr. Furguson: "Children are our future."
博爾克蘭先生說  "沒錯"
Mr. Berklan: "So true."
米勒先生說  "我要整理思緒
Mr. Miller: "I need to regroup.
"需要暫停一下  看這個
"I'm gonna stall a little bit. Watch this.
那個負責記錄的女士能否讀一下前面的部分"
Could the lady typer read that back?"
好了  好了  夠了
All right, all right, we've had enough.
我方恭謹地希望得到兩萬美元補償
My client is graciously willing to settle for $20,000.
作為真正的律師
As an actual real attorney,
我強烈建議你們接受協議
I highly suggest you take the deal.
-很好  我們會  -不可能
- Great. We'll do... - Not a chance.
那是不可能的
There's not a chance.
休息一下  過來施密特
Sidebar. Come on, Schmidt.
-趕緊的  -稍等
- Hurry up. - Just...
你不能接受那個和解
You are not taking that settlement.
尼克  至少賠了這兩萬美元
Well, Nick, at least if it's $20,000,
我就能擺脫這種困境了
I can get out of that hole some day.
我自有安排  你得給我機會
I've got a plan. You just have to give me a chance.
你能信任我嗎
Can you believe in me?
-好吧  我信任你  -成交
- All right, I believe in you. - Deal.
-成交  -你有什么安排
- Deal. - What's the plan?
我才不告訴你  你會生氣的  來吧
Oh, I'm not telling you. You're gonna get too mad. Let's go.
尼克  我收回剛才的話  我  我不信任你
Nick, I take it back! I don't... I don't believe in you!
這邊
Here.
這種比賽要多久
How long is this game?
上吧  教練
Go get 'em, Coach.
好吧聽著  你們這群平庸的傻孩子
All right, listen up, you no-talent, idiot babies!
把那東西給我  給我  給我
Give me that. Give me that. Give me that. Give me that.
謝天謝地
Oh, thank God.
集合
Bring it in.
過來
Come on.
那么  現在
All right, now,
誰會贏得比賽
who is gonna win this match?!
柯立芝
Coolidge!
誰是最棒的
Who's number one?
柯立芝
Coolidge!
大點聲  我們是
Let me hear it! Who are we?
-柯立芝  -埃姆
- Coolidge! - Rakim!
不是吧  埃姆  我剛教過你的
Really, Rakim? Like I just walked you right up to it,
而你  我們得談談
and you're gonna... We're gonna talk.
-柯立芝  -太遲了伙計  太遲了
- Coolidge! - Too late, man. It's too late.
好了伙計們  回賽場去  讓我驕傲一把
All right, guys, get out there and make me proud!
-戴老師  -干嘛
- Ms. Day? - What?
怎么回事  我以為你已經解雇了教練
What is going on? I thought you fired Coach.
聽著  教練愛孩子們  孩子們也愛他
Look, Coach loves the kids, and the kids love him.
我不想失去工作  但我也不會按你的方法做
I want this job, but I'm not going to do it your way.
我不會讓最佳人選離開的
I'm not going to let our best people go.
是你跟我說  我們沒有資金
You were the one who told me, we have no money.
是  但我們可以另想辦法  發揮創造力
Yeah, but we can make it up in other ways, we can be creative.
我們可以在課后
We can rent out the multipurpose room
把綜合教室租給當地社團俱樂部
after school to local clubs.
那管弦樂隊在哪里排練
And where will the orchestra practice?
你考慮過這個嗎  戴老師
Did you ever consider that, Ms. Day?
-還是你忙著買女士自行車了  -什么
- Or were you too busy buying a ladies bike? - What?
他們可以用圖書館
They can use the library.
反正也沒人去圖書館
No one goes in there anyway.
對  把書都燒了吧
Yeah, let's burn the books!
除了《達芬奇密碼》
Except for The Da Vinci Code.
感覺怪怪的  但是
Well, that took a weird turn, but...
謝謝你  蘇珊  簡直太好了
Thank you, Susan. That-that's so nice.
真是個好辦法
What a great solution.
加油  接住
Come on! Let's do it!
漢特  你個小野獸
Oh! Hunter, you animal!
好耶  來做機器人動作
Yeah! Hit the robot.
來做吧
Uh, uh, yeah, hit it.
我猜我們可以想出辦法留下他
I guess we can figure out some way to keep him here.
天啊  真拿你沒辦法
God, you frost my cookies.
謝謝
Thank you.
好耶
Way! Uh!
等一下  我在干嘛  回到賽場去
Wait, what am I... Get... get back out there.
比賽還沒結束呢
We got... We still have a game to play.
教練  你猜怎么的
Hey, Coach, guess what?
小心球
Ball!
沒關系
It's okay.
別笑  伙計們
Don't laugh, guys.
你們看到她臉被擊中了嗎
Did you see that hit her face?
我沒事  我還是坐下吧
I'm okay. I'm gonna sit down.
那么  你是要坐下呢還是
So, are you gonna sit, or...?
不  我站著好了
No, I'm gonna stand.
那不就是我們正在做的事嗎
'Cause isn't that what we are doing?
為了弱勢群體撐腰
Standing... for the little guy?
計劃是什么
What is the plan?
不公平
Injustice!
我不會再這么做了[雙關語  原意是站著]
I will not stand for it.
那就是我要坐下的原因
That is why I will sit right now.
我要坐在這把椅子上
I will sit down in this chair...
你太粗心了
You're negligent! Aah!
滾開  我的脖子  我的脖子
Get off me! My neck! My neck!
你在搞笑嗎  坐椅子也摔
Seriously? The fall-down on the chair bit?
-這是你的第一個案子嗎  -是的
- Is this your first case? - Yes, it is.
那就是我要為訴訟填寫訴狀的原因
And that is why I'll file petition on petition.
你需要早起完成文書工作
You're gonna wake up in the morning to paperwork.
晚上會伴著文書工作入睡
You're gonna go to bed at night to paperwork.
這樣如何  紳士們
So how about this, gentlemen?
如果你自己給你的委托人支付兩萬和解金
You pay the $20,000 settlement to your client yourself,
那么你就再也不會看到我們了
and you'll never see our faces again.
你們管只接過一個案子
What do you call a lunatic
而且沒有愛好的瘋子叫什么
who's only got one case and no hobbies?
你們最可怕的噩夢
Your worst nightmare.
走吧  伙計們
Let's go, guys.
聽著  比爾
Listen, Bill,
如果你真的想和大人們玩
if you ever want to play with the big boys,
給我打電話  好嗎
you'll give me a ring, won't you?
這是張棒球卡
This is a baseball card.
是啊
Yeah.
太棒了
All right!
-太棒了  你做到了  -我做到了
- All right. You did it. - I did it.
-干杯  -干杯
- Salud. - Cheers!
給爺滿上
Another round of shots.
-酒吧買單  -你不用說出來  溫尼
- On the house! - You don't get to say that, Winnie.
你知道的  對嗎  好吧
You know that, right? Okay.
我知道你會為了我而回來的
Oh, I knew you'd come back for me.
你現在想做什么呢  只是想開車嗎
So what do you want to do now? You want to just drive?
不  麥克
Oh, no. Mike!
-怎么了  -我來吧
- What? Ple... - I got it.
謝謝
Thank you.
你來這里做什么
Hey, what you doing here?
我只是想來說
I just wanted to come and say...
先說重要的
First things first.
澳大利亞的法定最低飲酒年齡是18歲
The legal drinking age in Australia is 18.
其次  你真的好漂亮
Second, you're really beautiful.
就好像  你真的好漂亮
Like, you're really beautiful.
就好像  我想約你出去
Like, I want to take you out some time.
但因為我已經二十歲了而且開局不好
But because I'm 20 and already at a bit of a disadvantage,
我覺得我需要做些非典型性行動
I thought I'd come and do some uncharacteristic
來改善你對我的印象
self-promotion to help the cause?
-好啊  -還有要告訴你
- Okay. - And let you know that
我剛剛開創了自己的事業
well, I just opened my own business.
我是造船的
I build boats.
手工建造木船
Uh, wooden boats with my hands.
老太太們很喜歡我
Um, old ladies love me.
她們說我很敏感
They call me sensitive.
而且我的廚藝很好
And I'm a really good cook.
但是我只會做三種食物
But I know three dishes,
其中兩種本質上還是同樣的東西
and two of those dishes are the same thing.
就是這些  你有什么想法
Yeah, that's about it, so, what do you think?
你想喝點什么嗎
Do you want to get a drink?
比如和你喝軟飲料嗎
Like a soft drink with you?
-軟飲料  散步  -你喝咖啡嗎
- Soft drink, a walk. - Can you have a coffee?
當然  我愛咖啡
Yeah, I love coffee.
那是我會做的三種食物之一
It's one of the three meals that I know how I make.
好吧
All right.
-出手啊  -干的漂亮
- Oh, do it! - Well done, sir!
你知道嗎  也許我們可以
Or you know what? We could actually...
也許我們現在就應該走
we could probably just go now.
我喜歡梳你的頭發  小妞兒
I'd like to comb your hair, you hunk.
我不認識他們
I don't know who they are.
他們是新來的  跑這里來撒酒瘋
They just come in here, and they drink, and make a lot of noise
還盡說些他們根本不懂的事
and talk about things they don't know about!
麥克  我要休息一下
Hey, Mike, I'm gonna take a break. Um...
我不知道什么時候回來  我在外面等你
I don't know when I'll be back. I'll just meet you out front.
停下你正在做的事
Stop what you're doing.
有個律師來
There's a lawyer here to make...
杰茜卡
Jessica?
杰茜卡  那個官司我贏了
Jessica, I won the case.
如果你現在醒來  我們可以打個炮
If you woke up right now, we could be making love.
杰茜卡
Jessica?
權勢夫婦
Power couple.
*Oh, I miss the comfort of this house*
*Where we are, where we are*